Now, the clouds in the sky are tropical yeah.
Your cheeks and the sun match, red.
Oh, tell me I'm the only one baby
I fancy you, I fancy you. (TWICE!)
It's dangerous it pricks you like a rose.
It's okay, I'm not one bit afraid.
Hold it hard, take my hand.
It will be a bit dangerous, even more dangerous baby.
Sweet like chocolate ice cream
My feelings are melting, so lovely.
Shining so bright in this dark universe.
The star, the star, and your star right next to mine.
Only you, I fancy you. I don't want anyone else.
Hey I love you!
(LOVE YA!)
Only you, I fancy you. We can be happy in our own dream.
'Cause I need you
(What?)
Fancy you~ Who cares who likes who first
Fancy you~  I will come to you first
Fancy (WOO!)
Everyday without you I can't do anything
Oh my Mayday, It will become very serious
Bang bang, I am hypnotized, my minds reset
What should I do, don't know if it is right S.O.S
Swim swim I'll be the submarine and you will be the sea
Every birthday is sweet You are my fantasy
Dream dream It's like I'm in a dream someone pinch me
Nowadays, my status is la la la baby
Sweet like chocolate ice cream.
My feelings are melting for you, so lovely.
Shining so bright in this dark universe
The star, the star and yours right next to mine.
Only you, I fancy you. No I don't want anyone else.
Hey I love you
Love ya
Yes only you, I fancy you. We can live a dream
Cause I need you
(What?)
Fancy you~ who cares who likes who first
Fancy you~ I will come to you first
Fancy (WOO!)
Will it suddenly disappear like smoke?
Always full of it, I take you in my eyes.
I become cozy by just thinking of you
I will secretly hold you from behind and never let go
Only you, I fancy you. No I don't want anyone else.
Hey I love you!
Love ya!
Yes only you I fancy you. We can live a dream
Cause I need you
What?
Fancy you~ who cares who likes who first
Fancy you~ I will come to you first
Fancy, (WOO)
English Subtitles by Rebecca Kathryn