This unwavering feeling of dreamin’
Motivates me all the time
Heading for an ideal future
I’m prepared to overcome any obstacles
Time is infinite but you can never turn it back
This story of “Me” only happens once
No matter what people say
Shake it off, I’m going my way
Say Say, Don't give up！
Till the day I can be proud of myself
Breakthrough Breakthrough
As time goes by
I will grow
The world awaits for me to shine
Say Say, Don't give up！
Break Break Breakthrough...
Everybody Break Break Breakthrough
Cast aside all doubts and grow up
My heart links now to the future
The beat is heating up, so keep movin’ on
Fight the weakness, gain strength through your heart
Break the limit baby, breakthrough Let go
Even if they compare me with others, I want to shout “me”
As long as I hold the milestone I aim for in my heart
Even in the tunnel with no light
Say Say, Don't give up！
Never look back, wanna keep moving on
Breakthrough Breakthrough
Continue to change
With the times
Gonna offer a new world with my dreams
Say Say, Don't give up！
Ah, what motivates me now has no reason
just the drive for tomorrow
No matter what people say
Shake it off, I’m going my way
Say Say, Don't give up！
Till the day I can be proud of myself
Breakthrough Breakthrough
As time goes by
I will grow
The world awaits for me to shine
Say Say, Don't give up！
Break Break Breakthrough...