Phone bell rings like every other day
Please give me a break
My battery’s running out
It keeps ringing and ringing
The phone might blow up any minute
He says I take his breath away
I get him all frustrated
I make his heart race why
He says I’m so pretty
Not that I’m bragging or anything
Oh, sorry for not answering
I was with my friend shy shy shy
Can’t see you right now, I’m sorry
I’ll call you later
Don’t urge me, it won’t take long
And I’ll let you call me baby
Now is not the time, it is too early
But show me a bit more
CHEER UP BABY
Give it a little more
A girl shouldn’t give her heart away so easily
That will make you want me more
I’ll pretend like I don’t care
So you don’t notice my feelings for you
just get it together and then baby
CHEER UP
I can just hear your anxious voice
I can just see your phone covered in sweat
Answering right away is no fun
I read your messages but ignore your calls
Uhh maybe I went too far boy
Worried I might tire out your patience
Uhh, but if I don’t, I might
Fall for you deeper, fall for you deeper
Oh, sorry I didn’t reply
I was with my friend shy shy shy
Can’t see you right now, I’m sorry
I’ll call you later
Don’t urge me, I’m not going anywhere
I will be your baby
Don’t be hasty, show some sincerity
I will wait for you
CHEER UP BABY
Give it a little more
A girl shouldn’t give her heart away so easily
That will make you want me more
I’ll pretend like I don’t care
So you don’t notice my feelings for you
just get it together and then baby
CHEER UP
I like you too, I’m afraid I might hurt you
But I hope you understand, I’m a girl after all
I’m afraid my feelings might show
Just come a little closer
It won’t be long
just get it together and then baby
CHEER UP
Be a man, a real man,
gotta see u love me like a real man
CHEER UP BABY
Give it a little more
A girl shouldn’t give her heart away so easily
That will make you want me more
I’ll pretend like I don’t care
So you don’t notice my feelings for you
just get it together and then baby
CHEER UP