I know there’s no point trying to change you
But unlike her, I am
not about to let go so easy (Never let go)
You don't know me
L O V E or hatred
Instead of goodbye I wear an innocent smile
Today I wanna be in your arms again
As if I don’t know anything
Baby no more real love
I will stay by your side
Then in the end break your heart
Bad boy bad boy
yeah you really make me
a mad girl mad girl
I want you to cry, cry for me
Just like I cried, Cry for me
Make your rain fall
Cry for me but
Again
Little by little I fall for you
Love makes my mind give way
And I keep making reasons to forgive
I want you to
Cry for me
I don't know but I just can’t seem to hate you
Always defending you in front of my friends
Made a fool of myself
Why do you keep smiling at me
Just one tear is all it takes
Cry for me, let me please forgive you
As if I don’t know anything
Baby just like real love
It’s your last chance c’mon
Show me your true love
Bad boy bad boy
yeah you really make me
a sad girl sad girl
I want you to cry, cry for me
Just like I cried, Cry for me
Make your rain fall
Cry for me but
Again
Little by little I fall for you
Love makes my mind give way
And I keep making reasons to forgive
I want you to
Cry for me
Love is so toxic
It makes hatred melt away
I want you again by my side yeah yeah
I want you to cry, cry for me
Even if it’s just pretend, Cry for me
Make your rain fall
fall and fall now
I want you to cry, cry for me
Just like I cried, Cry for me
Make your rain fall
Cry for me but
Again
Little by little I fall for you
Love makes my mind give way
And I keep making reasons to forgive
I want you to
Die for me