♪ Fake ♪
♪ True ♪
Fake & True ♪
If you long for what you do not have
In the end, it will not be tight
But if you have expectations,
One day it will certainly happen
♪ True True True ♪
Do not pretend to be the perfect person
Believe in your intuition
Weak energy is all that is needed
How long will it be until the limit is determined?
We can be more independent and brighter
♪ Hold on Fake & True ♪
♪ Fake & Fake & True ♪
Ake Fake & True ♪
Instead of giving up, give yourself a helping hand
It Get it now ♪
Do you also know what is best?
"Why can't I? I can't be!"
Open your brain for dreams and desires
♪ True True True ♪
When You Want Dreams
When those dreams come true (Ho)
You too
It must be amazing
Never ever say "I know I can't"
The happiness that comes when it is finally completed
LOVE LIFE FUN WORK
Canvas that will start to paint
For me, "Is this OK? Is that OK?"
Are the words sincere or a lie?
♪ Hold on Fake & True ♪
♪ Fake & Fake & True ♪
Ake Fake & True ♪
Do not hold back
It Get it now ♪
The most important thing is courage and imagination imigination
♪ Hold on Fake & True ♪
♪ Fake & Fake & True ♪
Ake Fake & True ♪
Instead of giving up, give yourself a helping hand
It Get it now ♪
Do you also know what is best?
English Subtitles by J.HetetMyet