Chaeyoung: There are one of those days
Days when I suddenly feel all alone(caption by IrmuunIrwin)
Chaeyoung: When I feel like I don’t belong anywhere
Chaeyoung: And my head is hanging down
Tzuyu: Whenever those days come, you tell me
How precious I am
Tzuyu: All those words you say
Momo(my bias); Everything’s alright
Momo: From Nobody to Somebody
Momo: I become a very special me
Sana: You make me feel special
Sana: No matter how the world brings me down
Sana: Even when hurtful words stab me
Sana: I smile again cuz you’re there
Sana: That’s what you do
Nayeon: Again I feel special
Nayeon: One moment I feel like I’m nothing at all
Like no one would notice if I were gone
Nayeon: But then when I hear you calling me
Nayeon: I feel loved, I feel so special
Mina(#wemissyoumina)/ Chaeyoung: I just wanted to hide
Didn’t wanna face the world
Mina/ Chaeyoung: As if everything has lost meaning
As if I have lost meaning
Mina/ Chaeyoung: I just sat there still
Momo: Then you appeared before me
With a warm smile, you held out your hand
Tzuyu: Everything’s alright
From Nobody to Somebody
I become a very special me
God Jihyo: You make me feel special
No matter how the world brings me down
Even when hurtful words stab me
I smile again cuz you’re there
That’s what you do
Jeongyeon: Again I feel special
One moment I feel like I’m nothing at all
Like no one would notice if I were gone
But then when I hear you calling me
I feel loved, I feel special
Dahyun(my bias wrecker): You make everything alright
On a cloudy day without sunshine
You are indeed my Shining light
That’s what you do
Even the darkest night turns to day
I owe it to you
Because you make me feel
Jihyo: You make me feel special
No matter how the world brings me down
Even when hurtful words stab me
I smile again cuz you’re there
That’s what you do
Nayeon: Again I feel special
One moment I feel like I’m nothing at all
Like no one would notice if I were gone
But then when I hear you calling me
I feel loved, I feel so special
dancebreak (SUB To IrmuunIrwin)
THANKS FOR WATCHING!!!