Lan la lan lan lan lan la la
Lan la lan lan la la
Oh yeah I wanna be with you
I feel it!  Destiny’s gimmick
Your smile, it’s just magic
The moment we met
Viva!  I’m over the moon Uh
My stubbornness disappears
I can be myself
There’s only one place I want to be
I know, I really really like you
Wanna tell you all about my dreams
And get closer to the ideal world
Can’t stop this romantic feeling
I feel Happy Happy Happy (U U U)
really glad that we met
No matter what happens
I wanna be with you
Happy Happy Happy (U U U)
I can imagine
We can bring our future vision to life
So I wanna be with you
Always, good times and bad times
We share, midnight
Feeling the same ups and downs
Twice as much joy, only half of the sadness
We’ll share together, let’s go
Can’t stop this excitement
So come on come on Leggo Leggo
As long as we’re together, we’ll be alright
Even on a bad day when I’m feeling down
Your words inspire me
Restart！You are my power
I'll be Happy Happy Happy (U U U)
I believe
Many years, many decades from now
I wanna be with you
Happy Happy Happy (U U U)
Anything is possible
We can overcome any challenges
So I wanna be with you
Yes Oh  because of you
Yes Oh  I can be strong
Yes Oh  you’re my everything
O-Oh I wanna be with you
Even in our next life
I believe we’ll meet again
Never ending Our love will never end
I wanna be there for you my love
Lan la lan lan lan lan la la
Lan la lan lan la la
Oh yeah I wanna be with you
Lan la lan lan lan lan la la
Lan la lan lan la la
Oh yeah
I feel Happy Happy Happy (U U U)
really glad that we met
No matter what happens
I wanna be with you
Happy Happy Happy (U U U)
I can imagine
We can bring our future vision to life
So I wanna be with you
Yes Oh because of you
Yes Oh I am inspired
Yes Oh forever and ever
O-Oh I wanna be with you