Alarm goes off Ring ring a ling
Whenever our eyes meet
I notice but just spin around
Yet I keep getting closer I know it’s too late
In my heart I already know
Sooner or later I’ll step over the line
I’m warning myself
You shouldn’t be doing this
Every minute, every second, my heart goes ahead of me
Out of control
I’m surrounded by that Spot spot spotlight
As it shines on me, I’m swept into the darkness
I see the end, I know it’s not right
I can’t stop me, can’t stop me
Right in front of me, this Red red red line
Across from each other, you and I exchange glances
Wanna feel the thrilling Highlight
I can’t stop me, can’t stop me
Keep your eyes closed Ya ya
Just this once No rules ah ah
Pretend you don’t know Lights off tonight
I can’t help it Losing myself
Now Turning back
Is impossible, I fall deeper into darkness
It is so thrilling
Wanna close my eyes
I just can’t go back anymore
Out of control
I’m surrounded by that Spot spot spotlight
As it shines on me, I’m swept into the darkness
I see the end, I know it’s not right
I can’t stop me, can’t stop me
Right in front of me, this Red red red line
Across from each other, you and I exchange glances
Wanna feel the thrilling Highlight
I can’t stop me, can’t stop me
Risky risky wiggy Crisis
This is an emergency
Help me, help me, somebody stop me
Cuz I know I can’t stop me
I already know the answer
But I still keep going
I don’t wanna do this
There must be another me inside me
I want it, but
Can’t do what I want
Guilty I don’t want it
I can’t stop me, can’t stop me, can’t stop me
I’m surrounded by that Spot spot spotlight
As it shines on me, I’m swept into the darkness
I see the end, I know it’s not right
I can’t stop me, can’t stop me
Right in front of me, this Red red red line
Across from each other, you and I exchange glances
Wanna feel the thrilling Highlight
I can’t stop me, can’t stop me