The door closes at twelve
Please hurry up a bit
Knock knock knock knock, knock on my door
At night inside my mind
The door opens up
I need somebody
(Someone else!)
You keep lingering around
Taking a sneak peek
Knock knock knock knock, knock on my door
Probably another playboy
Obviously just a bad boy
I need some assurance
(Knock knock!)
Knock on my heart and open it up
Knock hard Bam! Bam!
One more time Bam! Bam!
Baby, knock knock knock knock, knock on my door
Knock knock knock knock knock
It won’t be so easy to open it up
Come again tomorrow and the day after
I will be ready and waiting
Baby, knock knock knock knock, knock on my door
Knock knock knock knock knock
Wanna keep hearing it again
Knock on my door
No need for that gold key or get lucky
If you truly mean it everything’s gonna be okay
Oh no, you’re already here, could you please wait a moment
You pop in when I am alone
Shake me right out of my mind
Now is the perfect show time
(make it yours!)
Dang Dang when the clock strikes, would you come to me
Turn round round will only make you fall asleep
Knock knock knock knock, knock on my door
Come in, come in, come in baby, take my hands
Knock on my heart and open it up
Knock hard Bam! Bam!
One more time Bam! Bam!
Baby, knock knock knock knock, knock on my door
Knock knock knock knock knock
It won’t be so easy to open it up
Come again tomorrow and the day after
I will be ready and waiting
Baby, knock knock knock knock, knock on my door
Knock knock knock knock knock
Wanna keep hearing it again
Knock on my door
Hey, hey
After all this time
My frozen heart will, my my heart will
Melt away like an ice cream
Come knock on my door
Knock on my heart and open it up
Knock hard Bam! Bam!
One more time Bam! Bam!
Baby, knock knock knock knock, knock on my door
Knock knock knock knock knock
It won’t be so easy to open it up
Come again tomorrow and the day after
I will be ready and waiting
Baby, knock knock knock knock, knock on my door
Knock knock knock knock knock
Wanna keep hearing it again
Knock on my door
Knock knock knock knock on my door
I’m freakin’ freakin’ out, freakin’ out out, knock knock
Knock knock knock knock knock on my door