People just can’t leave me alone
Not for a single moment
I’m so pretty
I make everyone so smitten
No matter which way I go
The floors are all red
Like walking down the red carpet
Everyone is staring at me oh
Some people ask “who’s your mama?”
They take a fresh approach
But I don’t feel a thing
But I want to love somebody
Wanna fall in love Baby
Listen up my boy
I’m waiting for someone who can make me feel
Something like never before
(That’s who I’m waiting for)
I’ll wait no matter how long it takes
I just wanna fall in love
Keep me still
Make me like Ooh Ahh Ooh Ahh
Fake, fake, an empty-hearted fake
Goodbye and good riddance huh
(Like OOH-AHH)
Make me speechless
Make me like Ooh Ahh Ooh Ahh
Bla La La La stop talking, start doing
Make me feel Huh
(Like OOH-AHH)
Look at me and see me again
Pass by once and look back (TWICE)
Wherever I go, I go without makeup
But I’m the one who shines the most
Flat shoes can’t hide my high value
Movie-like scenes run through my head La La La
Just thinking about it makes me excited yeah
Now I want to love somebody
Wanna fall in love Baby
Listen up my boy
I’m waiting for someone who can make me feel
Something like never before
(That’s who I’m waiting for)
I’ll wait no matter how long it takes
I just wanna fall in love
Keep me still
Make me like Ooh Ahh Ooh Ahh
Fake, fake, an empty-hearted fake
Goodbye and good riddance huh
(Like OOH-AHH)
Make me speechless
Make me like Ooh Ahh Ooh Ahh
Bla La La La stop talking, start doing
Make me feel Huh
(Like OOH-AHH)
Don’t wanna start with just anybody
I’m not the kind of girl who gives herself away so easily
Let me see
How you gon treat me
I ain’t no easy
Better think about it TWICE
Let me see
How you gon treat me
I ain’t no easy
Better think about it TWICE
Keep me still
Make me like Ooh Ahh Ooh Ahh
Fake, fake, an empty-hearted fake
Goodbye and good riddance huh
(Like OOH-AHH)
Make me speechless
Make me like Ooh Ahh Ooh Ahh
Bla La La La stop talking, start doing
Make me feel Huh
(Like OOH-AHH)