(Hey!)
(Twice!)
Fluttering heart Me likey Me likey likey likey
Me likey likey likey
Pit-a-pat Pit-a-pat Heart Heart
Me Likey Me Likey Likey Likey
Me Likey Likey Likey
Pit-a-pat-Pit-a-pat
Keep wanting to show it all again and again
Every single little thing
Inside the small screen.
I wanna be the prettiest
Yet still I hide my feelings deep inside
It takes so much effort to get the perfect look
But it is something I can never give up
Makes my heart beat everyday,
It's something you must never know
Then I go on pretending
Bb cream pa-pa-pa,
Put on some lipstick mam-mam-ma
Pose for the camera, aren't I pretty?
When you see this,
make a smile,
and press hard
On that cute red  (Heart Heart) down there
Like is such a common word,
not enough to express my feelings.
But I like it,
even if I cant sleep,
even if i run late, like it anyway
Fluttering heart Me Likey Me Likey Likey Likey
Me Likey Likey Likey
Pit-a-pat Pit-a-pat (Heart Heart)
Me Likey Me Likey Likey Likey
I hold my breath to pull up the zipper,
tighten the waist again
Cheer me up, I'm done dressing up baby
There are so many pretty things to wear
(Woah~)
BB cream pa-pa-pa
put on some lipstick mam-mam-ma
Pose for the camera, aren't I pretty?
When you see this,
make a smile,
and press hard
On the cute red (Heart Heart) down there
Like is such a common word,
not enough to express my feelings
But I like it,
even if I can't sleep,
even if I run late, like it anyway
I just keep staring,
can't say anything
Oh~
Come a little closer, see how I feel
Don't wanna hide it anymore
I feel melancholy today,
pretend im not, but I still feel sad
I'm sulking cuz' you're not responding
My  insensitive friends are asking me to hang out
Oh~ wait wait I finally got an answer Woo!
My mind is swaying all day long
One moment I'm crying, then I'm dancing with excitement again
Fluttering heart Me likey Me Likey Likey Likey
Me Likey Likey Likey
Pit-a-pat Pit-a-pat (Heart Heart)
Me Likey Me Likey Likey Likey Me Likey Likey Likey
Thanks For reading