The best thing I ever did
December, as we end the year together, I remember
Our memories pile up like the snow
So many words I saved for you linger in my mind
Makes me nervous
Used to feel lonely and empty
But December is no longer lonely
The best thing I ever did
Was that I met you
The best thing I never did
Was that I never broke up with you,
and that I am still with you
All I wanna do All I wanna do
Just like this, like this, like this, like this,
the two of us forever
All I wanna do All I wanna do
Just like this, like this, like this, like this,
let us never change
Though I don’t notice, it just keeps showing
My friends are teasing that
I’m smiling from ear to ear the whole day
Even when I’m alone, I feel as if
You are behind me, my ears keep getting red
I can’t help it, I keep thinking of you
Used to feel lonely and empty
But December is no longer lonely
The best thing I ever did
Was that I met you
The best thing I never did
Was that I never broke up with you,
and that I am still with you
As the year goes by, Little by little
So many things have happened
But when I think about what they meant
Why are they the moments I spent with you
I think I might be in love
The best thing I ever did
Was that I met you
The best thing I never did
Was that I never broke up with you,
and that I am still with you
All I wanna do All I wanna do
Just like this, like this, like this, like this,
the two of us forever
All I wanna do All I wanna do
Just like this, like this, like this, like this,
let us never change
The best thing I ever did