Hey boy! Look, I'm gonna make this simple for you, (captions made by catjm)
You got two choices...
Yes or Yes?
Haaa~!
Choose only one, come on, yes or yes?
Since when was I so selfish?
Did I ever want something this eagerly?
Everyone is surprised at how shameless I am.
With my impudence.
(Come on and tell me yes!)
My scenario has become more daring than I thought.
I’d say this plan is perfect, quite satisfying
I don’t care no matter what others say!
(woo)
You better tell me yes!!
I have decided YES! Now it's time to hear your answer.
If it's too hard, there are examples to choose from. You don't have to waste your time thinking.
Don't know what you'll choose, so, I prepared these options
Choose only one of the two YES or YES?
Don't know what you want, so I prepared these options.
Make your choice come on YES or YES?
I will say no to your no, is it me or us?
I respect your choice but reject your rejection!
There is only one answer, the choice is up to you.
It's all up to you~!
Choose only one of the two YES or YES?
Do you mean it? Do not guess. Are you serious? Do not ask.
Don't give me that unsure side-to-side, I want a sure up and down!
There's no letters N & O. I'll erase them from today.
There's no need to think too hard. The answer is YES YES YO!
You bring out my hidden selfishness. Your eyes and my curiosity about you.
You make my heart burning. My heart burn burn burn!!
You better hurry up!
To make it simple. Whatever you choose, you will be with me.
Though it may seem a bit absurd. Though you might say I'm insisting you. I'll make you never regret it.
Don't know what you'll choose, so I prepared these options.
Choose only one of the two YES or YES?
Don't know what you want, so I prepared these options.
Make your choice come on YES or YES?
I will say no to your no, is it me or us?
I respect your choice but reject your rejection.
There is only one choice, the answer is up to you.
It's all up to you~!
Maybe not NO NO Maybe yes NO NO!
Make it clear. Show me how you feel!
Open your ears. Don't you hear it?
It's simple Y E S Hey
Choose only one of the two YES or YES? Make your choice come on YES or YES?
Here is one more YES or YES or YES
Take your pick, the choice is up to you.
Don't know what you'll choose, so I prepared these options.
Choose only one of the two YES or YES?
Don't know what you want, so I prepared these options.
Make your choice come on YES or YES?
I will say no to you no, is it me or us?
I respect your choice but reject your rejection.
There is only one answer, the choice is up to you!
It's all up to you~!
Make your choice come on YES or YES!